<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Search><pages Count="24"><page Index="1"><![CDATA[Happi   Birthda ,





                                        Wahy
































                                                                                           24.08.2023










































































                                                                                Fro  al  of your




                                                        camaraderi  an  con dant  a




                                    Managemen  an  Scienc  Universit  (MSU).]]></page><page Index="2"><![CDATA[]]></page><page Index="3"><![CDATA[]]></page><page Index="4"><![CDATA[]]></page><page Index="5"><![CDATA[Happy birthday to Kak Wahyu,Wishing you



                                                 much happiness on your special day and


                                                 success in all you do. Aamin ya rabb





                                                 (Nik)




















                                                 Happy birthday, Puan Manager! Thank you



                                                 for your constant support and dedication to


                                                 our social media team!



                                                 Note: Please refrain from singing without


                                                 music during office hours. If you do, I will



                                                 upload a video of you on TikTok.




                                                 (Zul)





















                                                 I want to wish one of our most skilled



                                                 person Kak Ayu a very happy birthday. You


                                                 are genuinely lovely on the inside and out,



                                                 kak. People are amazed by your kindness.



                                                 Wishing you the best on your birthday.


                                                 Happy Birthday, Kak Ayu!





                                                 (Hadi Wijaya)






















                                                 Congratulations! You’ve just become a



                                                 limited edition vintage. Happy Birthday.




                                                 (Miza)]]></page><page Index="6"><![CDATA[As we age looks may fade, but personalities



                                                 never change. Good thing it’s always been


                                                 about your personality! Happy birthday.






                                                 (Emma)

















                                                 Happy Birthday, Wahyu! May this special day bring


                                                 you well-deserved joy and relaxation. Perhaps this


                                                 time around Vesh should lead a choir to sing a


                                                 birthday song for you instead of always


                                                 accompanying you on stage as MC. Anyway, stay


                                                 true to good health, and may blessings be bestowed


                                                 upon you and your kin. Keep shining with your


                                                 remarkable performance!




                                                 (Hafizuddin)

















                                                Happiest Birthday kak ayu!! semoga Allah


                                                kurniakan kebahagian dunia akhirat, kesihatan



                                                yang baik, rezeki yang melimpah seperti air


                                                zam zam. Semoga Allah mudahkn urusan kak



                                                ayu pindah rumah baru . semoga Allah


                                                Kurniakan yang baik baik untuk kak ayu.



                                                Happy Birthday sis! have a blast !!!




                                                (Sakinah)






















                                                 HB Ayu, moga sihat sokmo & makin ohsem






                                                 (Hisham, Cedec)]]></page><page Index="7"><![CDATA[Barakallah fii umrik Ayu...Semoga panjang umur,


                                                 dimurahkan rezeki dan sentiasa dalam lindungan


                                                 & kasih sayang Allah SWT.






                                                 (Eli)





















                                                 Happy birthday to my wonderfully crazy and


                                                 kind-hearted friend. Your wild spirit and warm heart


                                                 make your truly special. Make your day be as vibrabt


                                                 & amazing as your personality. Here’s to more wild


                                                 adventures and moments of kindness. Celebrate big


                                                 and keep shining, your awesome soul





                                                 (Haliza)





















                                                 I want to wish one of our most skilled



                                                 person Kak Ayu a very happy birthday. You


                                                 are genuinely lovely on the inside and out,



                                                 kak. People are amazed by your kindness.



                                                 Wishing you the best on your birthday.


                                                 Happy Birthday, Kak Ayu!





                                                 (Hadi Wijaya)





















                                                 Happy Birthday, Ayuu!!! Hope u hv a fabulous



                                                 day ahead ... Forget-me-not,


                                                 ‘Lat-ta-li-lat ...



                                                 (K. Anis)]]></page><page Index="8"><![CDATA[‘Happy Birthday Ayu, may Allah bless you with


                                                 happiness, good health and success’







                                                 (Amlie)






















                                                 Salam Wahyu, Happy Birthday to you.


                                                 May Allah bless you always.


                                                 Moga sentiasa dimurahkan rezeki, dijauhkan dari


                                                 wabak dan kesihatan, dipermudahkan segala urusan


                                                 (urusan menjadi MC tetap MSU juga).


                                                 Be Happy and always Smile!






                                                 (Dr Imran, MSUMC)



























                                                 Happy Birthday Kak, Semoga Allah sentiasa



                                                 melindungi, memberkati dan merahmati…


                                                 Nnt jgn lupa share no kontraktor hahaha…








                                                 Your sparing partner, Nizam (IMS)

























                                                 Kepada Sahabatku , Wahyu Hidup bukan hanya



                                                 untuk dijalani, tapi harus disyukuri. Selamat


                                                 ulang tahun kelahiran untuk sahabatku..





                                                 (Syuk, CID)]]></page><page Index="9"><![CDATA[]]></page><page Index="10"><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Wahyu, Barakallahu fi 'umrik



                                                 Semoga dipanjangkan usia yang berkat,


                                                 dimurahkan rezeki, diberikan kesihatan,


                                                 sukses dunia akhirat





                                                 (Suif)






































































                                                Happy Birthday to you


                                                Happy birthday to Nurul Wahyu



                                                Happy Birthday to Youuuu



                                                Wishing your special day full of blessings love


                                                and happiness.



                                                May all your wishes come true





                                                (Hairol)






















                                                Ayu, wishing you nothing but the best today



                                                and always, happy birthday sis..i believe this



                                                year will bring wonderful things to you life.







                                                (Dr Haniza)]]></page><page Index="11"><![CDATA[Happy birthday wahyu semoga sentiasa dalam



                                                 lindungan ALLAH, dunia akhirat ..aamiin






                                                 (Noraida)




















                                                 Happy Birthday U



                                                 Wishing you a day filled with joy, laughter, and



                                                 all the things that make you smile. May this new


                                                 year bring you exciting adventures, personal


                                                 growth, and cherished moments with your loved



                                                 ones. Stay awesome and keep defying your


                                                 actual age!!




                                                 (Syamsu)






































































                                                Happy birthday my dear deq Wahyu..




                                                Semoga pnjng umur.. Murah rezeki.. Diberikan rezeki

                                                yg berkah.. Kesihatan yg baik.. Dalam rahmat n kasih

                                                sayang Allah sntiasa n beroleh kejayaan dunia


                                                akhirat, InsyaAllah aminn




                                                (Yatie Enrolment, EE)]]></page><page Index="12"><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Wahyu!!


                                                 May you be gifted with life’s biggest joys and



                                                 never-ending bliss.






                                                 (Ruzi)



















                                                 Happy Birthday, Wahyu!





                                                 Your support and dedication make every workday


                                                 brighter. Wishing you a day as wonderful as


                                                 you've made mine countless times.



                                                 Here's to another year of teamwork and success.


                                                 Enjoy your special day!





                                                 Love, Lisa




















                                                 Wishing you a fantastic birthday filled with joy


                                                 and blessings. Your straightforwardness has



                                                 always been a quality I admire, and it’s been a


                                                 pleasure working alongside you.







                                                 Cheers to another wonderful year ahead!







                                                 (Shauqi)























                                                 Happy birthday Wahyu..May Allah bless you


                                                 always..fly high and stay gorgeous vavaboom!







                                                 (Yatie, SESS)]]></page><page Index="13"><![CDATA[Happy birthday to a fantastic colleague Kak Ayu.


                                                 May God bless you with prosperity and



                                                 happiness.






                                                 (Azmi)





















                                                Dear Wahyu, om your birthday,i want to tell you,happy

                                                birthday to my beautiful Ms. Wahyu, May all the good things

                                                come to you.There's an old saying in China, which means that


                                                you will be able to encounter millions of good and happy

                                                things every years,and all the things will go smoothly.Today i


                                                pass on this wish to you,wish you more success joy and

                                                happniess than ever in the upcoming years. Happy birthday.


                                                All best,





                                                (Ailin)


























                                                Wishing you sannah helwah and happy birthday,


                                                KakYu, may the birthday celebration this year be a


                                                promise of a brighter year in your life and we wish


                                                you all the best on your special day.






                                                (Irfan)



























                                                Happy sweet xxth birthday XX,


                                                wishing you cheerful always and stress free







                                                (Fong)]]></page><page Index="14"><![CDATA[Wishing you a very Happy birthday. May your


                                                   birthday be the start of a year filled with



                                                  good luck ,health and happiness.






                                                  (Ahmad)



















                                                 Blessed birthday to the gorgeous Kak Ayu.


                                                 It’s true I was intimidated and had uneasy thoughts


                                                 about you — initially. However, things took a


                                                 different turn, and you are among the very few


                                                 people I look up to! On this special day and every

                                                 other day to come, I wish nothing but the best of the


                                                 ultimate best. Many more happy returns of the day!






                                                 (Abi)

























                                                 Count not the candles…see the lights they give.


                                                 Count not the years, but the life you live. Wishing


                                                 you a wonderful time ahead. Happy birthday Ayu!


                                                 Oh ya, best wishes on settling into your new place







                                                 (love, Fyda)




























                                                Happy Birthday Wahyu!! Wishing you a great day


                                                today and the year ahead with full of blessing!!






                                                (Azizul)]]></page><page Index="15"><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Kak Ayu


                                                 May Allah grant you all your desires & dreams on your special

                                                 day. May Allah also make your birthday a joyous occasion &

                                                 grant you all the happiness as well as success you deserve.


                                                 Enjoy your day to the fullest!



                                                 (Aishah, CEDEC)



















                                                Dearest Wahyu,


                                                I hope you see yourself the way I see you : amazing,


                                                incredible, kind, smart, compassionate, funny, and

                                                wonderful. I always admire your professional speaking


                                                skills and the ability to adjust to situational changes

                                                quickly. Happy Birthday Darling Wahyu


                                                Keep Rocking Dear





                                                (Pari)










































































                                                 Happy Birthday Wahyu


                                                 Semoga sentiasa didalam rahmat Dan redha Allah

                                                 & semoga success selalu.






                                                 Salam Sayang


                                                 (K.sata)]]></page><page Index="16"><![CDATA[Happy birthday Ayu!!


                                                  Love you!!






                                                  (Cik Nor)





















                                                 Happy Birthday, My dearest Kak Ayu


                                                 thank you for always, always hyping me up.


                                                 Somedays are really tiring and you have no idea how


                                                 your small gifts cheer me up and I forever grateful for all


                                                 the time you sparing for me, even when you are busy and

                                                 rushing from one meeting to another. May God bless you


                                                 and your family always Kak Ayu.


                                                 Hope you will have a year as great as you areee!



                                                 Love you, (Susan)























                                                 Sanah Helwah Mc!


                                                 Makin muda setahun dah


                                                 Semoga segala urusan dipermudahkan,


                                                 sentiasa dimurahkan rezeki, selalu belanja aku..



                                                 happy2 sokmo!!!






                                                 (Kamal)






















                                                 Happy birthday Ayu..DiDoakan semoga d kurniakan


                                                 kesihatan terbaik, d permudahkan segalanya &


                                                 success dunia akhirat dlm lindyngaNya..


                                                 Insya-Allah..Aminn...






                                                 (Madiy)]]></page><page Index="17"><![CDATA[Sanah Helwah to My Fav Person




                                                   i know you’re doing the best you can, i believe


                                                   in you. (we can go through this together sistur)





                                                   (luv : Sal)

















                                                   My dearest Ayu,



                                                   You are the kindest person i know.

                                                   i wish you could see yourself the way i see you and i wish you

                                                   could love yourself the way i love you. And above all, i wish


                                                   your life is everything you deserve because you deserve the

                                                   world. i will stand by you forever. Let this frenship in our heart

                                                   till jannah. For anything happen in your life, You're a warrior


                                                   and I hope you won't let you heart give up. Beauty is power but

                                                   smile is its sword! Keep smiling and shining. Happy Birthday

                                                   Ayu!



                                                   (Zura)
















                                                  Dear my Jannah Sohab,


                                                  Nurul Wahyu Razman.


                                                  Happy Birthday to the most amazing person I know!.

                                                  May your birthday be filled with joy, love and laughter,


                                                  and may your heart ber overflowing with happiness


                                                  throughout the coming year.


                                                  Fiamanillah Wahyu





                                                  (Nhiz)




















                                                  birthday wish for ayu :




                                                  happy birthday ayu. semoga sentiasa diberikan kesihatan

                                                  yg baik, dimurahkan rezeki, dipanjangkan umur dan hidup


                                                  sentiasa diberkati & dirahmati olehNya.

                                                  Barakallah Fii Umrik




                                                  (Azuan)]]></page><page Index="18"><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Ayu!


                                                   Semoga panjang umur dan sentiasa dalam


                                                   rahmat Nya






                                                   (Harris)

























                                                 Happy birthday, Kak Yu.


                                                 We make a unique emcee couple.


                                                 On to more and better!







                                                 (Vesh)


























                                                  Happy Birthday to our amazing colleague!


                                                  Your walls have witnessed countless dreams being


                                                  shaped, friendships blooming, and knowledge



                                                  flourishing. May the years ahead bring even more


                                                  inspiration, learning, and memorable moments.


                                                  Here's to another year of growth, success, and


                                                  unforgettable experiences!






                                                  (Fariz, YM)





















                                                Happy birthday to craziest sis.


                                                Our friendship always lifely and never dull when


                                                you're around..






                                                (Adnan)]]></page><page Index="19"><![CDATA[Meaning of Wahyu characters in chinese, harmony,


                                                 peace; peaceful, calm, fish;


                                                 Happy birthday to Wahyu (goreng pun sodap).


                                                 May Allah bless you always





                                                 (Indang)























                                                 Hye Wahyu,


                                                 Ipah Here...


                                                 Sanah helwah Sahabat !


                                                 Luv always






                                                 (Sh Hasbollah)


























                                               To Kak Ayu!




                                               Today is the day you were brought into this world to


                                               be a blessing and inspiration to the people around


                                               you! You are a wonderful person! May Allah bless you


                                               always amin.




                                               Sincerely,




                                               Izzul Azri



















                                                 This birthday, I wish you abundant happiness and


                                                 love. May all your dreams turn into reality and may


                                                 lady luck visit your home today. Happy birthday to


                                                 one of the sweetest people I’ve ever known.







                                                 [Hamidah]]]></page><page Index="20"><![CDATA[Happy Birthday, Wahyu! Your dedication and love for MSU


                                                is very impressive and totally contagious! We're all on the

                                                same page when it comes to that MSU spirit. Wishing you


                                                a day filled with laughter, good Times (no pun intended),


                                                and all the birthday treats you deserve!



                                                (Rajah)






















                                              Dear Kak Ayu,





                                              You're not just a colleague; you're like the guiding star


                                              of our workplace, always ready with a helping hand and

                                              a comforting word.





                                              Your knack for ensuring our snack cabinet is never empty


                                              and your uncanny ability to plan the most amazing

                                              celebrations have not gone unnoticed.





                                              You transform ordinary moments into cherished


                                              memories , creating an atmosphere of joy

                                              and togetherness.





                                              As the big sister of our department, you provide advice


                                              that's as precious as gold.





                                              Your wisdom and experience are a beacon for us all,

                                              guiding us through the twists and turns of our work with


                                              grace and confidence.





                                              May this birthday bring all the happiness you've brought

                                              into our lives. Here's to the moments we've shared and


                                              those yet to come.





                                              Thank you for being you, Kak Ayu!





                                              Happiest Sweet 40th Birthday!





                                               Semoga Allah panjangkan umur, murahkan lagi rezeki

                                              dan sentiasa sihat selalu. Amin





                                              Warmest wishes,


                                              (Farah Anis)]]></page><page Index="21"><![CDATA[Dearest Ayu.


                                                 Wishing you a day filled with happiness and a year filled


                                                 with joy. May you live long enough to see your hair grey


                                                 and your face wrinkled… but will never catch up with me!

                                                 Happy birthday dear!




                                                 (Prof Halinah)






















                                                 Happy Birthday Kak Ayu! May Allah


                                                 bring all the things in your life that

                                                 you're looking for. Your ability to


                                                 communicate effectively and thoughtfully


                                                 means so much. I hope you have a delightful

                                                 Birthday, Mentor!






                                                 (Amry)





















                                                  Dear Wahyu!





                                                  Sending you the warmest of wishes on this special day

                                                  of yours. Collaborating with you has been a seamless


                                                  and rewarding experience. May your day be filled with


                                                  joy and may the coming year bring you even more


                                                  success and happiness. Happy birthday!




                                                  (Nurbek from EasyUni)























                                                  Happy Birthday Wahyu semoga diberikan kesihatan


                                                  yang baik rezeki yang luas umur yang panjang dan


                                                  sentiasa ceria selalu hendaknya.






                                                  (En Hisham)]]></page><page Index="22"><![CDATA[Happiest birthday to you, Kak Wahyu!






                                                May your birthday be filled with sunshine and


                                                happiness, just like you brighten up the office every day.





                                                (Imran)
























                                                Don’t focus on getting another year older,


                                                just think of it this way... you’re one year closer

                                                to getting all those senior citizen perks!


                                                Happy Birthday.





                                                (Diha)












































































                                                  Sanah Helwah Puan Wahyu . Didoakan semoga


                                                  sentiasa dalam rahmat dan kasih sayang Allah


                                                  SWT...semoga tercapai segala yang dihajati. Aamiin





                                                  (Mimi, SBI)
























                                                wishing you a very happy birthday!


                                                May all your dreams come true.





                                                (Hafiz)]]></page><page Index="23"><![CDATA[]]></page><page Index="24"><![CDATA[]]></page></pages></Search>